嘿  瑞秋  我只是过来
Oh. Uh, hey, Rach. I was just coming over here to, uh...
等等  我没必要向你撒谎  你都搬走了
Oh, wait, I don't have to lie to you, you don't live here anymore.
我在吃他们的东西  你呢
I'm eating their food. What are you doing?
罗斯跟我妹约会
Ross is on a date with my sister.
窗帘已经拉上2个半小时了
They shut the drapes two and a half hours ago.
我们能跟你妹妹约会吗
Whoa, I didn't know we could date your sister.
乔伊  我们知道你在偷东西吃
Joey, we know you steal our food.
不用了
I'm good.
窗帘还没拉开
Oh, are the drapes still closed hon?
对  其实隔开两户的变态老夫妇  才应该拉上窗帘的
Yeah. And y'know who should've shut their drapes is that perverted couple two doors over.
那是秋千吗  不要问
Is that a swing? Oh, don't even ask.
罗斯居然跟瑞秋的妹妹约会
I can't believe Ross is going out with Rachel's sister.
钱德跟我妹亲热   我气了他10年
When Chandler made out with my sister, I was mad at him for 1O years.
那是5年前的事  对  你还剩5年
That was like five years ago. Yeah, you got five years left.
乔伊  你想再加1年吗
Joey-You wanna make it six?
老友记  第六季  第14集  谁是AV女优
Friends  S06E14  The One Where Chandler Can't Cry
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
罗斯  你好吗  你在这里
Oh, Ross, hey. Hi, how are you? There you are.
嘿
Hey.
一杯咖啡
Can I get a cup of coffee?
昨晚的约会怎样啊
So how was your big date last night?
还不错  很开心
Uh, it was okay. Yeah, it was fun.
是吗  对啊
It was fun? Yeah.
太好了
Great.
所以  你们合得来吗
So, uh... So did you guys hit it off?
应该吧  所以  那后来你们又怎么样嘛
I guess so. So, uh... So did anything happen?
听说你们把窗帘拉上了
Because rumor has it you guys shut the drapes. Heh.
不  不  我们没怎么样
No, no, nothing happened.
我是要放映我最爱的化石幻灯片
I shut the drapes to show her slides of my favorite fossils.
幻灯片啊
Oh, slides. Ha, ha.
所以你们真的没怎么样
So really nothing happened.
我们可以有怎么样  对了  她很喜欢我的幻灯片
Something could've happened, all right? She really dug my slides.
而且她绝对对我有放电
Mm. And she was definitely giving me the vibe.
是 "别再给我看三叶虫照片" 的电吗
Was it the "Please don't show me another picture of a trilobite" vibe?
总之
Anyway...
要是她不喜欢我   为什么要再约我
If she wasn't into me, why would she ask me out again?
她又约你了  对啊
She asked you out again? Yeah, uh-huh.
明天晚上
Tomorrow night. Hmm.
一年之中最浪漫的日子  情人节
Valentine's Day. The most romantic day of the year.
谁知道会怎样
Who knows what could happen?
到时候我拉上窗帘   或许就不是要放幻灯片了  你懂吧
I might not be shutting my drapes to show her my slides, if you know what--
当然   我懂  我懂了
Okay, okay, okay, I got it, I got it.
我不能接受你跟我妹交往
I can't-I can't go with the you-and-my-sister thing.
我就是不能  那样太奇怪了  好吗
I just can't. It's just too weird, all right?
一想到你们在一起  我就抓狂
I imagine the two of you together, I freak out.
我会疯掉的  我受不了  我受不了  好了  好了  别激动
It just freaks me out, and I can't do it. Okay, okay, okay. No-Yes. It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
如果你受不了  我就不再见她
Hey, it's too weird for you. I won't see her again.
谢谢你  我是说过了明晚之后
Thank you. I-Yeah. I mean, after tomorrow night.
不不不  求求你  罗斯  我受不了  我真的会捉狂的
No, no, no. Please, Ross. I can't do it. It's gonna freak me out.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
好  我今晚就告诉她  我不能再跟她见面了
Okay. I'll tell her tonight I can't see her anymore.
罗斯  谢谢
Ross, thanks.
你要我现在打给她吗  不  不用
You want me to call her right now? Oh, no. No, no, no.
那样太夸张了
I mean, come on, that's craz-I mean, that's crazy.
怎样啊  你最近在干嘛
So, what's going on with you? What is going on with you?
这个嘛
Well, um... Oh.
我这学期可能会再开一堂课  好啊  现在就打给她
I may teach another class this semester. Yeah, do it now. Call her right now.
我最喜欢这段了  我也是
This is my favorite part. Yeah, me too.
你们知道什么更催泪  《小鹿斑比》
Oh, you know what's sadder than this? Bambi.
那部片让我哭了3天  不  是2天
I cried for three days with that movie. No, wait, two.
第三天我妈自杀了  我也在哭那件事
Because on the third day, my mother killed herself, so I was partly crying for that.
为了那个哭我可以了解   但是《小鹿斑比》是卡通片啊
Well, see, now, that I can see crying over, but Bambi is a cartoon.
斑比的母亲死了  你没哭
You didn't cry when Bambi's mother died?
对啊  动画师不再画母鹿了  的确很可怜
Yes, it was very sad when the guy stopped drawing the deer.
钱德   哭没什么不对  你不必老是那么男子汉
Chandler, There's nothing wrong with crying. You don't have to be so macho all the time.
我哪有男子汉啊
I'm not macho.
也对
Yeah, you're right.
我不知道我在想什么
I don't know what I was thinking.
反正我就是没哭过   我不是那种会哭的人
I guess I just never really cried, you know? I'm not a crying kind of guy.
少来啊   你总会遇见令你鼻酸的事
Come on, man, there's gotta be something that gets you choked up.
像
Like, uh...
如果你看到一只三脚小狗呢
What if you saw a three-legged puppy?
我是会难过   但是不会哭
I'd be sad, sure, but I wouldn't cry.
要是那只小狗说  "钱德救救我
Okay, what if the puppy said, "Help me, Chandler.
其他的狗狗都欺负我"
All the other puppies pick on me."
哭啊  我发现了一只会说话的狗   我发了
Cry? I just found a talking puppy. I'm rich.
我知道了  你小时候的照片
Oh. I've got it. I have got it. Pictures from your childhood.
你看了一定会哭
This will get you going good.
那张是什么  那是年级的家长会
All right, what's going on there? Oh, that's Parents' Day, first grade.
我和校工马丁的合影
That's me with the janitor, Martin.
你爸妈呢   他们不想去
Where are your parents? Oh, they didn't wanna come.
钱德  好可怜啊
Oh, Chandler. You poor thing.
这件事不会让你哭吗
So that story doesn't make you cry?
不会  我就是不会哭  这没什么  好吗
No. Look, I don't cry. It's not a big deal, okay?
不  不好  一点也不好
No. It's not okay. It's not okay at all.
你的心是死的
You're dead inside.
请问一下  什么事
Excuse me. Yeah?
你是菲比布非吗   是我
Are you Phoebe Buffay? Yeah.
可以帮我签名吗   我是你的超级粉丝
Can I get your autograph? I'm your biggest fan.
你是我的超级粉丝  我一直想认识你   你好
Oh, you're my biggest fan? I've always wanted to meet you. Hi. Ha, ha.
没问题
Sure, yeah. Wow.
谢谢你
Wow, thanks a lot.
我只想说  你真的很有天分
I just wanna say I think you're really talented.
你是因为崇拜我才这么说的
You're just saying that because you're my biggest fan.
乔伊   好好招呼那个人  他是个影迷
Joey, listen, take good care of that guy. okay? He's a fan.
再见
Bye.
你看过我演的《我们的日子》
So you saw me on Days of Our Lives, huh?
要我来一段  德瑞克雷莫瑞医生吗
Want me to, want me to do a little Dr. Drake Ramoray for you?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
不过我刚拿到菲比布非的签名
But I just got Phoebe Buffay's autograph.
你是菲比的影迷  没错  她的电影我都看过
Oh. You're Phoebe's fan. Oh, yeah. I've seen all her movies.
电影  那是菲比布非  AV巨星
Movies? That was Phoebe Buffay, the porn star.
不是吧  不  不  是她
I don't think so. No, no, it was.
她演过《性玩具总动员》
She was in Sex Toy Story 2...
《女人国的劳伦斯》
...Lawrence of a Labia.
而我拿到了她的签名
And I got her autograph.
漫画店的人一定不会相信
The guys at the comic-book store aren't gonna believe this.
阿甘
Gunther.
以后别让那个人进来   他说菲比是AV巨星
Hey, don't let that guy in here anymore. He just said Phoebe's a porn star.
说巨星有点夸张了  不过她真的很猛
Well, I wouldn't call her a star, but she's really good.
你应该去看《G歪神探》
You should check out Inspect Her Gadget.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
说了你一定不信
You'll never believe what just happened.
罗斯刚刚回绝我  又没说原因
Ross totally blew me off and didn't even tell me why.
这个嘛  你知道吗
Oh, well. You know what, honey?
忘掉一个男人最好的办法   就是跟其他人交往
The best thing to do to get over a guy is to start dating someone else.
我们公司有个鲍伯  你一定喜欢
Oh. Oh, there is this great guy you will just love at work named Bob.
他是人力资源部的明日之星
He's a real up-and-comer in Human Resources.
谢谢你替我打气   但我不想随便跟某个阿猫阿狗交往
Y'know, thanks for trying to cheer me up, but I’m not gonna date some random guy from your work.
不是阿猫阿狗  是鲍伯
Not random. Bob.
可能是因为我不够成熟  不够聪明
It's probably because I'm not mature enough or smart enough.
或许他不喜欢我的打扮
Maybe he doesn't like the way I dress.
不可能的   一定是我不够聪明
No, that can't be it. It's really gotta be the smart thing. Ugh.
我好笨
I'm so stupid.
我是个美得冒泡的笨女人
I'm just this, like, incredibly pretty, stupid girl.
不是
No, honey.
好吧
0Kay.
你知道罗斯为何取消约会
Okay. You wanna know why Ross canceled the date?
是我要求的
Because I asked him to.
你要求的   嗯嗯
You asked him to? Mm-hm.
为什么   因为你是我妹妹
Why? Because you are my sister...
而罗斯和我有一大段爱的渊源
...and Ross and I have this huge history.
我不懂   你想跟罗斯交往吗  不想
I don't understand, do you want to go out with Ross? No.
你不要他  又不要我拥有他
You don't want him, but you don't want me to have him?
人力资源部的鲍伯
You know, Bob in Human Resources... Ugh.
你居然这样对我   你害的我怀疑我的智商
I cannot believe you did this to me. You had me doubting how smart I was.
你害的我怀疑我的穿着品味
You had me doubting my fashion sense.
这又不是什么大事  我只是叫你不要跟罗斯约会
This is not that big a deal. You just don't date Ross.
世上的男人那么多  你没有资格教我做什么
There's a million other guys out there. Hey! You have no right to tell me what to do.
我不是在教你做   我是在教你不要做
I'm not telling you what to do. I am telling you what not to do.
你为什么老是这么嫉妒我   不是我嫉妒你
Why are you always so jealous of me? This is not about me being jealous of you.
是你太任性  不能吃还想吃
This is about you being a brat, wanting what you can't have.
不能吃
Can't have?
很抱歉   我不能吃的东西只有乳制品
Excuse me, the only thing I can't have is dairy.
好  你和鲍伯的事吹了
All right, all right. You just blew your chances at dating Bob.
谁  人力资源部的啦
Who? In Human Resources!
我嫉妒她
I am jealous of her?
她以为她是谁  卡洛琳公主吗
I mean, who does she think she is, Princess Caroline?
你嫉妒卡洛琳公主  我有自己的城堡吗
You're jealous of Princess Caroline? Do I have my own castle?
嘿   菲比不在吧
Hey. Phoebe's not here, is she?
不在  真好  你们租了片子
No. Oh, great, did you get a movie?
嗯
Uh...
耶
Yeah. Yeah.
但是  我想你们应该不会喜欢吧
But, uh, I don't think it's the kind you're gonna like.
你该不会又租那种  整夜消耗纸巾的片子吧
You didn't get more movies that are gonna have us reaching for the tissues all night, did you?
也可以这么说
Sort of.
到底怎么了
Guys, what's going on?
菲比是AV女优
Phoebe's a porn star.
什么  对
What? Yeah.
你在说什么啊   哪里有
What are you talking about? Where?
"菲比布非之《魔法欲女》"
"Phoebe Buffay in Buffay the Vampire Layer."
天哪  这是菲比  你在哪里租的
Oh, my God. Ha, ha. That's Phoebe. Where did you get that?
布里克街的成人录影店
Down at the adult video place on Bleecker.
我看到乔伊正要进去  就先跑进去
And I saw Joey was about to go in, so I ran in ahead of him...
准备吓他
...to surprise him.
然后我又假装不知道他也在
And then-Ha, ha. Then I pretended that I didn't know he was in there.
天哪  我真是不敢相信
Wow. I mean, I just can't-I can't believe this.
真是知人知面不知心啊
You know? I mean, you think you know someone.
虽然菲比一直是个问号
even, Even Phoebe, who's always been somewhat of a question mark.
好诡异啊
This is so bizarre.
不过  毕竟她的童年那么悲惨
I guess it kind of makes sense, though. She had such a terrible childhood.
我童年悲惨也没去拍A片啊
Hey, I had a terrible childhood and I don't do porn.
对  但是你的心死了
Yes, but you're dead inside. Ah.
好吧  我还是拿去还了吧  什么  为什么
All right, well, I'd better take that back. What? Why? Why?
我们不能看  那是菲比演的
We can't watch that. I mean, that's Phoebe.
你说得对  我们不该看  没错  拿去还
Yeah you’re right, We shouldn't watch this. Absolutely not. That goes back.
看一点好了  就看前半段
But, you know, maybe a little bit. How about just the first half?
嘿  这样不对啊   菲比是我们的朋友
Hey, no, this is wrong, you guys. Phoebe's our friend.
我不看   没错
I'm not gonna watch it. Yeah.
有义气   乔伊  对
Good for you, Joe. Yeah.
我就知道你在这里  纳斯佛拉吐
Ah. I thought I'd find you here, Nosferatool.
布非  你要把你的尖棍   深深插进我的体内吗
Buffay, are you going to plunge your stake into my dark places?
其实  我有点希望是你来插我
Actually, I was kind of hoping it would be the other way around.
等等  她的脚踝上是什么  你在看她的脚踝
Hold on, what is that on her ankle? Her ankle is what you're watching?
很难看得出来
Well, it's hard to tell. Ooh.
她能不能不要动了
Oh, God, if she would just stop moving.
她只是在尽本分
She's just doing her job.
你们这些变态
You sick bastards.
是刺青  怪了  菲比可没有
Oh. It's a tattoo. That's weird. Phoebe doesn't--
等等   那是乌苏拉  不是菲比  是乌苏拉
Wait, that's Ursula. That's not Phoebe. That is Ursula.
等等  我可以看了  快倒带
Wait, wait. I can watch that. Rewind it. Rewind it.
嘿  哇哦
Hey. Oh.
你们在干麻  天哪  我在干什么
What's up? Oh, my God. What am I doing?!
《心灵鸡汤》
亲爱的  嘿
Hey, sweetie. Hey.
《心灵鸡汤》
Chicken Soup for the Soul?
这张沙发背后是空的
There's no back to this couch.
你看它干嘛  你不是讨厌这种书嘛
Why are you reading this? You hate this kind of stuff.
我想试试看
Yeah I know, but I figured a shot y'know?
也许有某个故事会让我哭
Maybe one of those stories would make me cry.
你就不会觉得我的心死了
Then you wouldn't think I was all dead inside.
你真有心
Aw, that's so sweet.
钱德  你不会哭也无所谓  我爱你
Chandler, I don't care if you can't cry. I love you.
这话温暖了我空空如也的胸口
Oh, that makes me feel so warm in my hollow tin chest.
别闹了  拜托  你想嘛
Stop it. I mean, come on, seriously. Think about it.
哪天我们结婚了  来到神父面前  我却是这样
We get married, I'm up at the altar, and I'm like this:
我不在乎
I won't care.
因为我知道你内心充满喜悦
Because I know that you'll be feeling it all in here.
是吗  当然
Yeah? Yeah.
要是有一天我们生小孩
And if we have a baby one day...
医生在产房把宝宝交给你
...and the doctor hands it to you in the delivery room...
而你没有哭   那又怎样
...and you don't cry, so what?
要是我们送他去念大学  然后回家
And if we take him to college and we come home...
第一次看到他的空房
...and we see his empty room for the first time...
而你却没反应
...and you got nothing?
我也不在意
Won't matter to me.
好
0Kay.
那我就不那么担心了
Well, I won't worry about this anymore, then.
那么  如果要是我死了
Yeah. And, you know, if I die...
久病弃世
...from a long illness...
你在写哀悼词
...and you're writing out my eulogy...
然后打开抽屉  看到我留了一张字条写道
...and you open the desk drawer and find a note from me that says:
"我会永远与你同在"
"I will always be with you"...
而你还是挤不出一滴眼泪
...and you still can't shed one tiny tear...
我会知道  你的心早已泪流成河
...I know you'll be crying a river inside.
我真爱你  怎么搞的
Aw, I love you, sweet-What is wrong with you?
什么  什么
What? What?
你居然无法为亡妻流一滴眼泪
You can't shed a tear for your dead wife?
我死后留了字条给你
I mean, I left you a note from the beyond.
所以刚才都不是真心话   废话  死机器人
So you didn't mean any of that? No, you robot!
死小孩  再乱按电铃  我就
You damn kids. You ring my bell one more time, I swear to--
吉儿
Oh, uh, Jill. Um...
我在跟走廊那头的小朋友玩
That's just a little game I play with the kids down the hall.
他们越来越喜欢我了
They've really taken a liking to me.
有什么事吗
What's the matter?
瑞秋和我大吵了一架   我可以进去吗
Rachel and I had a really big fight. Can I come in?
我知道我们不能再见面   我也可以接受
I know we're not supposed to see each other anymore. I'm okay with that.
只是我人生地不熟  又很需要找个人谈一谈
I don't know anybody in the city, and I need somebody to talk to about it.
好啊  怎么了  我不想谈
Oh, of course. What happened? I don't wanna talk about it.
好
Okay. Um...
不过有一件事会让我比较开心   什么事
But you know what might really cheer me up? What?
再多看几张你的超酷幻灯片
Seeing some more of your super-cool slides.
真的吗   绝对的  我爱死了
Wow, really? Totally. I loved them.
你还可以继续讲解  那几种不同的沙子
And maybe you could finish telling me about all the different kinds of sand.
没问题  你等一下  我去拿投影机和讲义
I'd love to. You wait right here. I'll go get the projector and my notes.
太好了  谢谢你  你真是个好朋友
Oh, great. Thanks, Ross. You're such a good friend.
哇啊
Oh.
嘿  你们有看到吉儿吗   我到处都找不到她
Hey. Have you guys seen Jill? I can't find her anywhere.
没看到   在罗斯家吗
No, I haven't. ls Ross home?
我打过去问他好了
Maybe I'll just call him and see if he's actually seen her.
哪一位
Who is it?
是菲比   "菲比"
It's Phoebe, "Phoebe."
嘿  天哪
Hey. Oh, God.
所以你在拍A片  没有  我没有啊
So you're making porn movies. No, I'm not.
摄影机还在拍
We're still rolling.
你现在就在拍
You're making one right now.
菲比  快点  而且还用我的名字
Let's go, Phoebe. And you're using my name.
对  有什么事吗
Yeah, can I help you with something?
菲比  快点
Phoebe, come on.
我在跟别人说话   你是在叫她
Look, I'm talking right now. You're-You mean her. Oh.
双胞胎的题材一向很卖
You know, twin stuff is always a real big seller.
什么
What?
我可以帮你谈到30块钱
Yeah. I could talk them into giving you like $30.
不要  想都别想
No. No way. No.
别再冒用我的名字  你真丢脸
And stop using my name. And shame on you.
你们真丢脸   恶心死了
And shame on all of you. You're disgusting.
尤其是你那个样子
Especially you, with that.
幻灯片快好了
Slides are almost ready.
好  我知道还少了什么
Yeah. Ooh, I know what this is missing.
酒
Alcohol.
好  厨房有红酒  太好了
Okay, well, there's wine in the kitchen. Oh, great.
哈罗
Hello?
我妹妹为什么在你家   窗帘为什么拉上了
What is my sister doing there, and why are the drapes shut?
好  你别激动
Okay. Rash, calm down, okay?
她心情很差   我们只是在聊天
She's really upset. We're just talking.
罗斯  她想借此跟你发生关系   来报复我
I think she's trying to make something happen with you to get back at me.
所以她来  只是为了这个
Oh, so that's the only reason she could be here, huh?
会不会是因为我很善于倾听
It couldn't have anything to do with the fact that I'm a good listener...
而且放的幻灯片又很好看呢
...and I put on a great slide show?
罗斯  是真的  她在利用你来报复我
Ross, I am telling you, she is using you to get back at me.
我自己可以应付  回头再聊  再见
You know, I think I can take care of myself. I'll talk to you later. Goodbye.
是你姐姐打来的
Uh, that was your sister, actually.
她觉得你在利用我
She thinks you're just using me. Heh.
所以呢
So?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我刚去过了乌苏拉的公司
So I just came from the company Ursula works for.
连你  你也下海了
Oh, no, not you too.
不  我是去领菲比布非的支票
No, no. I went to pick up Phoebe Buffay's checks.
有很多张啊
There were a lot of them.
漂亮
Nice. Mm-hm.
而且我以后不必再去了
And I won't have to go back there anymore...
我留了我的 "正确" 地址
...because I gave them my "correct address."
太好了  但别人还是会误会   你不会困扰吗
That's great, but isn't it gonna bother you that people think you're a porn star?
不   不会的   我有办法
Oh, no, no. I know how to handle it.
是吗  没错
Good. Yeah.
想知道你在哪里见过我
You're trying to figure out where you know me from?
给你一个提示  成人A片  好吗
All right, I'll give you a hint. From porn. Okay?
没错  你的变态男朋友  在A片里看过我
Yeah, your pervert boyfriend watched me in a porno movie!
看吧  对啊
See? Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
你对吉儿的看法或许没错   我就知道  怎么了
You, uh, may have been right about Jill. Oh, I knew it. What happened?
她吻了我   什么  你们都亲嘴了
Um, she kissed me. What? You kissed?
也许我们应该回避一下
Maybe we should give them some privacy. Shh!
我尽量不去亲她
Look, I tried not to kiss her, okay?
听起来不像   想不亲一个人
It doesn't sound like it. It's pretty easy not to kiss someone.
不要亲就对了  我们现在  就没有亲
You just don't kiss them. See? Look at us right now, not kissing.
让我说完好吗
Let me finish, okay?
她过来亲我   我没有阻止
She started kissing me, and I didn't stop it.
而且我也没有多想
I guess I just wasn't thinking.
是啊   没有多想   我来让你好好想一想
Yeah,  that's right you weren't thinking! Y'know what? Let me give you something to think about.
等等
Hold on.
后来我一想  就把她推开了
But then I started thinking and I stopped the kissing.
谢谢你把舌头  从我妹的嘴里缩回来告诉我
Oh, well, thank you for taking your tongue out of my sister's mouth long enough to tell me that.
我是想到  如果我跟吉儿怎样
Look, I realized if anything were to happen with me and Jill...
我们就再也不能怎样了
...then nothing could ever happen with us.
什么  不  我是说
What? No, I mean...
我不知道  我们还会不会怎样
Look, I don't know if anything is ever going to happen with us again, ever.
但我不想断绝这个可能性
But I don't wanna know that it never could.
于是我喊停
So I stopped it...
然后  她气得摔坏了我的投影机
...and she got mad and broke my projector.
哇哦
Wow.
我都不知道该说什么了
I don't even know what to say.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我的天哪   你在哭吗
Oh, my God, are you crying?
这两个人为何就是不能在一起
I just don't see why those two can't work things out.
好  我要走了  我要远离某个
All right, I'm leaving. I'm not gonna spend one more day...
一直害我的人
...with someone who's out to sabotage my every move.
就是你   瑞秋
That's you, Rachel.
我知道
Yeah, I got that.
还有你  我投怀送抱  你却不要
And you. I throw myself at you, and you say no?
你够同性恋的啊
How gay are you?
你自己保重   吉儿
You take care, Jill.
好  再见  再见
Okay, see you. Bye-bye.
吉儿居然走了
I can't believe Jill's gone.
我忍不住了  我一发不可收拾
I can't help it. I opened a gate.